I hope I can get my shoes back.
I know it's cheap,
but I don't want
to buy another one.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SWEETLY]
Mr. Jeon, housekeeping!
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- He's not home.
- [DOOR UNLOCKS]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXCLAIMS]
Where could it be?
[EXHALES]
These feet are meant to go far.
To the bus, the terminal,
and the pawnshop.
For Mama.
For Mama's surgery.
I can do this.
Hannah, you can do this.
[GROANS]
Oh, god. Where could it be?
Goodness.
That man's such a headache.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DANIEL] Huh. You again.
- [GASPS]
[GASPS LOUDLY]
Sir!
Sir, uh...
[STAMMERING]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Sir...
Cover, please!
Please, uh, cover up.
Sir, please, put--
[SCREAMS]
[SULTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
Sir...
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry...
Big mistake.
Big, big, big, big...
[GASPS]
Big?!
[GRUNTS] You pervert!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]